opg.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy | OPG

### **Privacy policy**

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for opg.com. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website and notifies you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

####  **Information collection, use, and sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We will only collect personal information where you provide consent for us to access and retain it for purposes we identify. This Privacy Policy identifies the personal information we intend to collect and the purpose for doing so. By accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy you consent to such collection. If we intend to collect any other personal information not identified in this Privacy Policy or intend to use the personal information identified in this Privacy Policy for a purpose not identified here, then we will notify you of the intended collection and seek your consent to do so for the purposes we identify. We may also collect, retain, use or disclose personal information without your consent in limited and specific circumstances as set out in the _Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act_.

We will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. We may engage third party service providers to process personal information on our behalf, but such third parties will be restricted to using personal information only for the purposes we set out and may not use or disclose it for any other purpose.

We may collect your personal information, including your name, feedback, contact and web-activity information for one of the following purposes: (1) to send messages to subscribers to the community or project newsletter(s) (e.g., The Darlington Refurbishment Project Newsletter) and (2) to sign up or register for community programs. Voluntary survey information may also be collected and may be used for a variety of internal purposes to review and improve the services we provide.

We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as set out in this Privacy Policy or as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to share news and updates relevant to your original inquiry, or changes to this Privacy Policy. Any such communications you receive from us will comply with all applicable law and will include an option for you to unsubscribe or “opt-out” of receiving such communications in the future.

####  **Your access to and control over information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#304755525d5143445542705f40571e535f5d):

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

####  **Security**

When you submit sensitive information via the website, we take precautions to protect your information both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information, it is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to address your inquiry are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

We employ all reasonable industry standard measures to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or destruction of the information we collect and our levels of safeguards correspond to the level of sensitivity of the information. While we are committed to ensuring the security of the information, no protection measure can provide a 100% guarantee of security. Consequently, we cannot warrant or guarantee the security of the information. We retain your information for as long as necessary or relevant for the listed purposes in this Privacy Policy, or as required by any applicable legal and retention obligations.

#### Signing up for a community or project newsletter and community programs

When signing up for a community or project newsletter (“Newsletter”) or community programs, a user is required to provide certain information that will be used to contact the individual regarding the Newsletter or the community programs you sign up for. Third-party vendors will collect and store the information that you provide to sign up for the Newsletter or community programs in the following ways:

  * The information that you provide when completing a form is stored in the WordPress content management system. Ninja Forms also collects this information via the Ninja Forms plug-in; the information is subsequently sent to Mailchimp to provide you with the Newsletter subscription services that you signed up for.
  * SendGrid’s email delivery platform will be used to send emails from the site; as such, they will also receive and store the email address that you provide.

####  **Sharing**

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

####  **Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

####  **Pixel tags and cookies**

Your interaction with our website and digital services may put you in contact with pixel tags and cookies. Pixel tags are small bits of code that provide a method of delivery information on a webpage, which allows the operator of the page or a third party to collect your IP address. Cookies are small pieces of file data that are stored on your computer or other device when websites are loaded in a browser. Cookies can collect digital use data that support a number of functions, including: basic necessity cookies required to authenticate and perform account related functions; advertising; functionality and preference support; performance indicators; tracking; and third party/embedded content. Many browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change your browser settings to refuse cookies or be alerted when a cookie has been placed on your browser.

####  **Analytics**

To enable us to improve our services and improve your experience, we partner with WordPress and Google Analytics to obtain aggregated and anonymized information about user data. Our partners will collect user data for the purpose of preparing statistical reports that we will use to review and improve our services. You may have the option to opt out of default user data collection practices via certain browser settings, using third party browser plug-ins and other privacy controls.

####  **Surveys and contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

 **If you feel that Ontario Power Generation is not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at[ [email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#9eeeecf7e8fffde7b0f1f8f8f7fdfbecdef1eef9b0fdf1f3)**.
